thegeneraldirectory.net 2012-12-10

# Forex Trib — Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. This notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This notice is available on our homepage.

ForexTrib.com does not collect personally identifying information with the sole exception of your specific knowledge and consent thereof. We do not share such information with any third parties, and no third party has access to your stored information.

ForexTrib.com stores all information in password protected directories and publicly inaccessible databases. ForexTrib.com will never sell or distribute email addresses and/or other personally identifying information to third parties without your explicit permission, nor use it for unapproved commercial purposes.

Like all sites, ForexTrib.com keeps detailed logs of site usage. Statistics tracked include country of origin, your browser type, IP address and the pages you request. This information is used to find out which parts of a site are most popular and to provide aggregate marketing information to clients. Detail information about your browsing habits is not disclosed to third-parties.

We do not sell your personal information to third-parties, however we may occasionally send mails to users on behalf of third-parties. Users may opt-out of these mailings.

We will not send mails for Viagra, casinos, pyramid schemes, pornography, nor other generic spam.

We may send all registered users regular email updates on the ForexTrib.com system. We may send all registered users email when ForexTrib.com launches new services. Users may opt-out of these mailings.

To participate for ForexTrib.com discussions and comments you are required to provide a valid email address. We track the IP address of every posting on ForexTrib.com discussions. We may remove personally identifiable postings where necessary.

No personally identifiable information is collected for our polls.

We may conduct surveys on behalf of third-parties. Any information collected will be used by third-parties in their marketing efforts. We will always ask all third-parties to use information gathered in surveys responsibly. However, we have no control over how the third-party uses the information collected.

We may write one or several cookies to your machine to track your progress through the site. No personally identifiable information can be collected from these cookies.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

All online credit card transactions are performed only on secure servers through a secure SSL connection. Credit Card information for recurring payments is not stored on our public servers.

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information.

ForexTrib.com reserves the right to reveal registration information pursuant to a valid subpoena or court order. We reserve the right to use or share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of ForexTrib.com’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

We will transfer information about you if ForexTrib.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

At any time, you may review or update your personal information by contacting us via the contact form available online. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. Please do not hesitate to contact us if you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy.

The above is subject to change at any time without notice whatsoever.
